A Guide to the Harry F. Byrd Jr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Legislative Files
  - Commerce: Bicycles & Motorcycles, 1973-1977 (Box Box 111)
  - Commerce: Buses, 1973-1982 (Box Box 111)
  - Commerce: Census, 1973-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 112)
  - Commerce: Communications, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 112)
  - Commerce: Consumer Protection Agency, 1974 (Box Box 112)
  - Commerce: Consumer Protection Agency, 1975-1977 June-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 113)
  - Commerce: Consumer Protection Agency, 1977 January-May, 1978-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 114)
  - Commerce: Consumer Protection & Complaints, 1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 114)
  - Commerce: Consumer Protection & Complaints, 1974-1976 June-August; (8 folders) (Box Box 115)
  - Commerce: Consumer Protection & Complaints, 1976 January-May; (2 folders) (Box Box 116)
  - Commerce: Consumer Safety Act (S. 3419), 1972 (Box Box 116)
  - Commerce: East-West Trade Agreement, 1973-1981 (Box Box 116)
  - Commerce: Federal Communications Commission, 1972-73, 1975-1976 July-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 116)
  - Commerce: Federal Communications Commission, 1976 January-June, 1977-1978, 1979 May-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 117)
  - Commerce: Federal Communications Commission, 1979 February-April, 1980-1981; (6 folders) (Box Box 118)
  - Commerce: Federal Trade Commission, 1972-1977; (2 folders) (Box Box 118)
  - Commerce: Federal Trade Commission, 1978-1980; (7 folders) (Box Box 119)
  - Commerce: Federal Trade Commission, 1981-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 120)
  - Commerce: Foreign Exports, 1973-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 120)
  - Commerce: Foreign Imports, 1973-1979; (7 folders) (Box Box 121)
  - Commerce: Foreign Imports, 1980-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 122)
  - Commerce: Foreign Investments, 1973 & 1977 (Box Box 123)
  - Commerce: Foreign Trade, 1973-1978 May-November; (5 folders) (Box Box 123)
  - Commerce: Foreign Trade, 1978 January-April, 1979-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 124)
  - Commerce: Foreign Trade Tariffs, 1973-1980 (Box Box 124)
  - Commerce: Holidays, etc., 1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 124)
  - Commerce: Holidays, etc., 1974-1977; (7 folders) (Box Box 125)
  - Commerce: Holidays, etc., 1978-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 126)
  - Commerce: Interstate Commerce Commission, 1973-1974 (Box Box 126)
  - Commerce: Interstate Commerce Commission, 1975-1980; (8 folders) (Box Box 127)
  - Commerce: Interstate Commerce Commission - Colonial Transit, 1975 (Box Box 128)
  - Commerce: Maritime & Sea, 1973-1980; (7 folders) (Box Box 128)
  - Commerce: Mass Transit, 1973-1974 (Box Box 128)
  - Commerce: Metric System, 1973-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 129)
  - Commerce: Metro and Mass Transit, 1974-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 129)
  - Commerce: Patent Laws, 1974 (Box Box 129)
  - Commerce: Patent & Copyrights, 1973-1974; (2 folders) (Box Box 129)
  - Commerce: Patents & Copyrights, 1975-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 130)
  - Commerce: Public Broadcasting, 1973-1981 (Box Box 130)
  - Commerce: Radio, 1973-1975; (2 folders) (Box Box 130)
  - Commerce: Radio, 1976-1982 (Box Box 131)
  - Commerce: Railroads, 1973-1975; (6 folders) (Box Box 131)
  - Commerce: Railroads, 1976-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 132)
  - Commerce: Railroads - Amtrak, 1973 (Box Box 132)
  - Commerce: Railroads - Amtrak, 1974-1979; (8 folders) (Box Box 133)
  - Commerce: Railroads - Amtrak, 1980-1981 (Box Box 134)
  - Commerce: Railroads - Northeast Crisis, 1973-1974 (Box Box 134)
  - Commerce: Russian Wheat Sales, 1973 (Box Box 134)
  - Commerce: Telephone, 1976-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 134)
  - Commerce: Television, 1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 134)
  - Commerce: Television, 1975-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 135)
  - Commerce: Transportation - General, 1973-1976; (2 folders) (Box Box 135)
  - Commerce: Transportation - General, 1977-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 136)
  - Congress, 1975-1977 April-December; (3 folders) (Box Box 136)
  - Congress, 1977 January-March, 1978-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 137)
  - Congress: Chaplain of the Senate, 1973-1981 (Box Box 137)
  - Congress: Committees, 1972-1978, 1979 October-November; (9 folders) (Box Box 138)
  - Congress: Committees, 1979 January-September, 1980 December; (9 folders) (Box Box 139)
  - Congress: Committees, 1980 July-November; (7 folders) (Box Box 140)
  - Congress: Committees, 1980 January-June; (7 folders) (Box Box 141)
  - Congress: Committees, 1981 August-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 142)
  - Congress: Committees, 1981 April-July; (7 folders) (Box Box 143)
  - Congress: Committees, 1981 January-March, 1982 August 23-30, September-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 144)
  - Congress: Committees, 1982 April-August 19; (8 folders) (Box Box 145)
  - Congress: Committees, 1982 January-March; (4 folders) (Box Box 146)
  - Congress: Committees - Appropriations (Barinaga), 1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 146)
  - Congress: Committees - Armed Services, 1973 (Box Box 146)
  - Congress: Committees - Armed Services, 1974-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 147)
  - Congress: Committees - Armed Services (Defense Speech), 1974 (Box Box 147)
  - Congress: Committees - Armed Services (Intelligence), 1977-1979, n.d.; (2 folders) (Box Box 148)
  - Congress: Committees - Armed Services (Mid-East Trip), 1979 (Box Box 148)
  - Congress: Committees - Democratic Policy Committee, 1977 & 1982 (Box Box 148)
  - Congress: Committees - Ethics, 1974, 1976-1982 (Box Box 148)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance, 1972-1974; (3 folders) (Box Box 148)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance, 1975-1978 September 12-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 149)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance, 1978 May-September 11; (8 folders) (Box Box 150)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance, 1978 January-April, 1979 October 9-31, September-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 151)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance, 1979 July-October 5; (6 folders) (Box Box 152)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance, 1979 March 22-June; (7 folders) (Box Box 153)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance, 1979 January-March 1-20, 1980 September-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 154)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance, 1980 June-August; (5 folders) (Box Box 155)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance, 1980 January-May, 1981 April-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 156)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance, 1981 January-March, 1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 157)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance (Child Welfare and Title XX), 1979 (Box Box 157)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance (Financial Markets), 1973-1974 (Box Box 157)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance (International Finance & Resources), 1973; (3 folders) (Box Box 157)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance (International Finance and Resources), 1974-1975 (Box Box 158)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance (Press Releases), 1973 (Box Box 158)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance (Private Pension Plans), 1973-1974 (Box Box 158)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance (Sugar Act Amendments H.R. 8866), 1971; (4 folders) (Box Box 158)
  - Congress: Committees - Finance (Trade Reform Bill), 1974 (Box Box 158)
  - Congress: Committees - House of Representatives, 1976 (Box Box 159)
  - Congress: Committees - Judiciary, 1981-1982; (9 folders) (Box Box 159)
  - Congress: Committees - Judiciary (Malt Beverages), 1981 (Box Box 160)
  - Congress: Committees - Reorganization, 1976-1977; (4 folders) (Box Box 160)
  - Congress: Committees - Rules, 1973-1978; (4 folders) (Box Box 160)
  - Congress: Committees - Rules, 1979-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 161)
  - Congress: Committees - Rules (S. 372), 1972-1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 161)
  - Congress: Congressional Record Index, 1974 (Box Box 161)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Byrd, Robert C., 1980-1981 July-November; (2 folders) (Box Box 161)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Byrd, Robert C., 1981 January-June, 1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 162)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Colleague Referrals, 1975-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 162)
  - Congress: Correspondence - House of Representatives, 1973 (Box Box 162)
  - Congress: Correspondence - House of Representatives, 1974-1977; (8 folders) (Box Box 163)
  - Congress: Correspondence - House of Representatives, 1978-1982; (8 folders) (Box Box 164)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1973-1974 July-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 165)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1974 January-June, 1975 August-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 166)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1975 January-July; (7 folders) (Box Box 167)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1976-1977 October-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 168)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1977 February-September; (7 folders) (Box Box 169)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1977 January, 1978 August 11-31, September-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 170)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1978 March-August 10; (7 folders) (Box Box 171)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1978 January-February, 1979 August-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 172)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1979 March-July; (6 folders) (Box Box 173)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1979 January-February, 1980 April-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 174)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1980 January-March, 1981 July-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 175)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1981 January-June, 1982 July-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 176)
  - Congress: Correspondence - Senate, 1982 January-June; (4 folders) (Box Box 177)
  - Congress: House of Representatives - Hays,Wayne, 1976 (Box Box 177)
  - Congress: Library of, 1974-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 177)
  - Congress: New York City Bailout, 1975 December (Box Box 177)
  - Congress: New York City Bailout, 1975 September-November; (7 folders) (Box Box 178)
  - Congress: New York City Bailout, 1976-1979 (Box Box 179)
  - Congress: Pay Legislation, 1973-1975; (6 folders) (Box Box 179)
  - Congress: Pay Legislation, 1976-1977; (8 folders) (Box Box 180)
  - Congress: Pay Legislation, 1978-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 181)
  - Congress: Powers and Responsibility, 1973 (Box Box 181)
  - Congress: Ralph Nader Reports, 1972-1977 (Box Box 181)
  - Congress: Roll Call Votes, 1977-1980 (Box Box 181)
  - Congress: Senate, 1974-1982 (Box Box 181)
  - Congress: Senate Leadership, 1973-1977 (Box Box 181)
  - Congress: Sergeant at Arms, 1974-1982 (Box Box 181)
  - Congress: Travel, 1977-1982 (Box Box 181)
  - Congress: Wednesday Morning Group, 1973 (Box Box 182)
  - Courts, 1975-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 182)
  - Courts: Confirmations, 1967-1977 (Box Box 182)
  - Courts: Confirmations, 1978-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 183)
  - Courts: Confirmations - Judgeships - A-C, ca. 1965-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 183)
  - Courts: Confirmations - Judgeships - D-M, 1965-1981; (5 folders) (Box Box 184)
  - Courts: Confirmations - Judgeships - M-T, 1966-1981; (6 folders) (Box Box 185)
  - Courts: Confirmations - Judgeships - W, 1969-1979; (2 folders) (Box Box 186)
  - Courts: Confirmations - U.S. Attorneys - A-Z, 1966-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 186)
  - Courts: Confirmations - U.S. Magistrates - A-Z, 1979 (Box Box 186)
  - Courts: Confirmations - U.S. Marshalls - A-Z, 1964-1981 (Box Box 186)
  - Courts: Domestic Relations, 1974-1978; (2 folders) (Box Box 187)
  - Courts: Domestic Violence, 1980 (Box Box 187)
  - Courts: Federal, 1973-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 187)
  - Courts: Federal Legal Aid Service, 1973-1977 (Box Box 187)
  - Courts: Impeachment, 1973 (Box Box 187)
  - Courts: Judges - Byrd Amendment, 1972-1973 January (Box Box 187)
  - Courts: Judges - Byrd Amendment, 1973 February-December, 1974-1981; (6 folders) (Box Box 188)
  - Courts: Judicial Advisory Commission, 1977 October-December (Box Box 188)
  - Courts: Judicial Advisory Commission, 1977 February-September, 1978; (6 folders) (Box Box 189)
  - Courts: Judicial Advisory Commission, 1979-1980 April 17-October; (5 folders) (Box Box 190)
  - Courts: Judicial Advisory Commission, 1980 February-April 16, 1982 (Box Box 191)
  - Courts: Judiciary, 1975-1981 (Box Box 191)
  - Courts: State, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 191)
  - Courts: Supreme Court, 1968 September 11-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 191)
  - Courts: Supreme Court, 1968 June-September 10; (7 folders) (Box Box 192)
  - Courts: Supreme Court, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 193)
  - Courts: Traffic Violations, 1974-1981 (Box Box 193)
  - Crime and Criminals, 1973-1975 August-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 193)
  - Crime and Criminals, 1975 January-July, 1976-1979; (7 folders) (Box Box 194)
  - Crime and Criminals, 1980-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 195)
  - Crime and Criminals: Capital Punishment, 1973-1975 (Box Box 195)
  - Crime and Criminals: Capital Punishment, 1976-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 196)
  - Crime and Criminals: Correspondence with Criminals, 1973-1974; (3 folders) (Box Box 196)
  - Crime and Criminals: Correspondence with Criminals, 1975-1977; (5 folders) (Box Box 197)
  - Crime and Criminals: Correspondence with Criminals, 1978-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 198)
  - Crime and Criminals: Department of Justice, 1977-1982 (Box Box 198)
  - Crime and Criminals: Drugs, 1980-1982 (Box Box 198)
  - Crime and Criminals: Federal Bureau of Investigations, 1976-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 198)
  - Crime and Criminals: Gun Control, 1972-1973 January-March (Box Box 198)
  - Crime and Criminals: Gun Control, 1973 April-December, 1974, 1975 August-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 199)
  - Crime and Criminals: Gun Control, 1975 March 19-July; (6 folders) (Box Box 200)
  - Crime and Criminals: Gun Control, 1975 January-March 18, 1976-1977; (6 folders) (Box Box 201)
  - Crime and Criminals: Gun Control, 1978-1979; (5 folders) (Box Box 202)
  - Crime and Criminals: Gun Control, 1980-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 203)
  - Crime and Criminals: Juvenile Delinquency, 1973-1982 (Box Box 204)
  - Crime and Criminals: Law Enforcement, 1973-1977; (5 folders) (Box Box 204)
  - Crime and Criminals: Law Enforcement, 1978-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 205)
  - Crime and Criminals: Miscellaneous Crimes, 1973-1982 (Box Box 205)
  - Crime and Criminals: Prisons and Penalties, 1980-1982 (Box Box 205)
  - Defense, 1973-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 205)
  - Economy, 1972, 1973 October-December (Box Box 205)
  - Economy, 1973 January-September, 1974; (6 folders) (Box Box 206)
  - Economy, 1975-1978, 1979 November-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 207)
  - Economy, 1979 March-October; (5 folders) (Box Box 208)
  - Economy, 1979 January-February, 1980; (7 folders) (Box Box 209)
  - Economy, 1981 February 19-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 210)
  - Economy, 1981 January-February 18, 1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 211)
  - Economy: Appalachia, 1973-1979 (Box Box 211)
  - Economy: Debt Ceiling Bills, 1971-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 211)
  - Economy: Disaster Assistance, 1973-1977 (Box Box 211)
  - Economy: Economic Development, 1973-1978 (Box Box 212)
  - Economy: Office of Economic Opportunity, 1973-1974 (Box Box 212)
  - Economy: Par Value Modification (H.R.6912 & S. 929), 1973 (Box Box 212)
  - Economy: Population Growth, 1973-1976 (Box Box 212)
  - Economy: Price Controls, 1973 May-December; (5 folders) (Box Box 212)
  - Economy: Price Controls, 1973 January-April, 1974 October-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 213)
  - Economy: Price Controls, 1974 January-September; (6 folders) (Box Box 214)
  - Economy: Price Controls, 1975-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 215)
  - Economy: Small Business Administration, 1973-1978; (2 folders) (Box Box 215)
  - Economy: Small Business Administration, 1979-1982 (Box Box 216)
  - Economy: Small Business Administration (Old Dominion Sugar Corporation), 1970 (Box Box 216)
  - Education, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 216)
  - Education: Arts and Humanities, 1973-1981 (Box Box 217)
  - Education: Bills, 1971-1972 (Box Box 217)
  - Education: Culture, 1971-1982 (Box Box 217)
  - Education: Education Amendments of 1972 (S. 659) (Box Box 217)
  - Education: Elementary and Secondary, 1973-1977; (2 folders) (Box Box 217)
  - Education: Elementary and Secondary, 1978-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 218)
  - Education: Federal Aid, 1973-1976 (Box Box 218)
  - Education: Federal Aid - Grants, 1973-1982 (Box Box 218)
  - Education: Federal Aid - Headstart, 1973-1981 (Box Box 218)
  - Education: Federal Aid - Impacted Area Aid, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 219)
  - Education: Handicapped, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 219)
  - Education: Higher Education, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 220)
  - Education: Libraries, 1973-1980 (Box Box 220)
  - Education: Private Schools, 1972-1977 (Box Box 220)
  - Education: Public Schools, 1974-1978 (Box Box 221)
  - Education: School Lunch Program, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 221)
  - Education: Sports and Athletics, 1973-1980; (3 folders) (Box Box 222)
  - Education: Student Loans, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 222)
  - Education: Teacher Education, 1972-1974 (Box Box 222)
  - Education: Vocational Education, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 223)
  - Education: Vocational - The Rehabilitation Act of 1972 (S. 7 & H.R. 8395), 1972-1973 (Box Box 223)
  - Energy, 1975-1979 November-December; (5 folders) (Box Box 223)
  - Energy, 1979 June-October; (7 folders) (Box Box 224)
  - Energy:, 1979 January-May, 1980-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 225)
  - Energy: Alternate Sources, 1980-1981 (Box Box 225)
  - Energy: Carter's Policy, 1977-1979; (5 folders) (Box Box 226)
  - Energy: Coal, 1975, 1980-1981 (Box Box 226)
  - Energy: Conservation, 1980-1981 (Box Box 226)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1973 December 7-28; (6 folders) (Box Box 227)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1973 November 20-30, December 1-6; (6 folders) (Box Box 228)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1973 June-November 19; (6 folders) (Box Box 229)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1973 January-May, 1974 May-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 230)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1974 February 22-28, March-April; (6 folders) (Box Box 231)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1974 January 23-February 21; (6 folders) (Box Box 232)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1974 January 1-21, 1975 October-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 233)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1975 May-September; (6 folders) (Box Box 234)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1975 January-April; (6 folders) (Box Box 235)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1976-1977 October-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 236)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1977 May-September; (6 folders) (Box Box 237)
  - Energy: Crisis, 1977 January-April, 1978; (7 folders) (Box Box 238)
  - Energy Crisis, 1979-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 239)
  - Energy: Department of, 1978-1980; (3 folders) (Box Box 239)
  - Energy: Department of, 1981-1982 (Box Box 240)
  - Energy: Electric, 1973-1974; (2 folders) (Box Box 240)
  - Energy: Federal Energy Administration, 1976 & 1979 (Box Box 240)
  - Energy: Federal Power Commission, 1974-1975 (Box Box 240)
  - Energy: Gasoline & Natural Gas, 1976-1980; (3 folders) (Box Box 240)
  - Energy: Gasoline & Natural Gas, 1981-1982 (Box Box 241)
  - Energy: Hampton Roads Refinery, 1974-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 241)
  - Energy: Nuclear, 1973-1975; (3 folders) (Box Box 241)
  - Energy: Nuclear, 1976-1979; (7 folders) (Box Box 242)
  - Energy: Nuclear, 1980-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 243)
  - Energy: Oil, 1974-1978, 1979 December; (3 folders) (Box Box 243)
  - Energy: Oil, 1979 July-November; (7 folders) (Box Box 244)
  - Energy: Oil, 1979 March-June, 1980 January 20-31, February-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 245)
  - Energy: Oil, 1980 January 1-18, 1981-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 246)
  - Energy: Rural Electric & Telephone Direct Loan Programs Bill (S. 394), 1973 (Box Box 246)
  - Energy: Solar, 1973-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 246)
  - Energy: Synfuels, 1980-1982 (Box Box 246)
  - Energy: Taxes, 1977 October-December (Box Box 246)
  - Energy: Taxes, 1977 August-September, 1978-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 247)
  - Energy: Tennessee Valley Authority, 1974-1981 (Box Box 247)
  - Energy: Utility Rates & Regulations, 1974-1980; (4 folders) (Box Box 247)
  - Energy: Utility Rates & Regulations, 1981 (Box Box 248)
  - Federal Government, 1975-1977; (7 folders) (Box Box 248)
  - Federal Government, 1978-1980 June-December; (9 folders) (Box Box 249)
  - Federal Government, 1980 January-May, 1981; (7 folders) (Box Box 250)
  - Federal Government, 1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 251)
  - Federal Government: Bids & Contracts, 1973-1980, 1981 January-August; (3 folders) (Box Box 251)
  - Federal Government: Bids & Contracts, 1981 September-December, 1982 (Box Box 252)
  - Federal Government: Buildings, 1973-1981; (5 folders) (Box Box 252)
  - Federal Government: Commission to Reduce Paperwork, 1974-1979; (2 folders) (Box Box 252)
  - Federal Government: Commuter Tax, 1976-1978 (Box Box 252)
  - Federal Government: District of Columbia, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 253)
  - Federal Government: District of Columbia - Firemen & Police Salaries & Retirement, 1976-1978; (2 folders) (Box Box 253)
  - Federal Government: District of Columbia - Operations, 1973-1981 (Box Box 253)
  - Federal Government: District of Columbia - Revenue Act of 1975, 1975 September-October (Box Box 253)
  - Federal Government: District of Columbia - Revenue Act of 1975, 1975 August (Box Box 254)
  - Federal Government: Home Rule, 1973-1981 (Box Box 254)
  - Federal Government: Housing & Urban Development, 1981-1982 (Box Box 254)
  - Federal Government: Procurement, 1974 (Box Box 254)
  - Federal Government: Regulations & Procedures, 1975-1981 (Box Box 254)
  - Federal Government: Reorganization, 1973-1978; (4 folders) (Box Box 254)
  - Federal Government: Reorganization, 1979-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 255)
  - Federal Government: Reorganization (Employee Parking), 1979 (Box Box 255)
  - Federal Government: Senior Citizens, 1978 (Box Box 256)
  - Federal Government: Surplus Government Property, 1973-1982 (Box Box 256)
  - Federal Government: Treasury Department, 1979-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 256)
  - Foreign Relations, 1973-1975 June-December; (3 folders) (Box Box 256)
  - Foreign Relations, 1975 January-May, 1976-77 November-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 257)
  - Foreign Relations, 1977 January-October, 1978 November-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 258)
  - Foreign Relations, 1978 January-October; (7 folders) (Box Box 259)
  - Foreign Relations, 1979, 1980 June-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 260)
  - Foreign Relations, 1980 January-May, 1981; (7 folders) (Box Box 261)
  - Foreign Relations, 1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 262)
  - Foreign Relations: Africa, 1973-1978; (4 folders) (Box Box 262)
  - Foreign Relations: Africa, 1979-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 263)
  - Foreign Relations: Angola, 1975-1977 (Box Box 263)
  - Foreign Relations: Arab-Israeli Conflict, 1973 October 19-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 263)
  - Foreign Relations: Arab-Israeli Conflict, 1973 October 5-18, 1974-1977, 1978 May-November; (8 folders) (Box Box 264)
  - Foreign Relations: Arab-Israeli Conflict, 1978 January-April, 1979-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 265)
  - Foreign Relations: Cambodia, 1973-1975 April-June; (4 folders) (Box Box 265)
  - Foreign Relations: Cambodia, 1975 March, 1977-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 266)
  - Foreign Relations: Central America, 1981-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 266)
  - Foreign Relations: Chile, 1973-1976 (Box Box 266)
  - Foreign Relations: China - Communist & Nationalist, 1972-1978; (2 folders) (Box Box 266)
  - Foreign Relations: China - Communist & Nationalist, 1979-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 267)
  - Foreign Relations: Council on Foreign Relations, 1981-1982 (Box Box 267)
  - Foreign Relations: Cuba, 1973-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 267)
  - Foreign Relations: Cuba, 1980-1982 (Box Box 268)
  - Foreign Relations: Debts, 1975-1976 (Box Box 268)
  - Foreign Relations: Egypt, 1974-1978 (Box Box 268)
  - Foreign Relations: El Salvador, 1981-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 268)
  - Foreign Relations: Foreign Aid & International Development, 1973 (Box Box 268)
  - Foreign Relations: Foreign Aid & International Development, 1974-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 269)